Guide to the Dept. of Dairy Industry records, 1903-1961.
Dept. of Dairy Industry records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Dairy Industry records, 1903-1961.
21-20-450
New York State College of Agriculture. Department of Dairy Industry.
30.2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, financial records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence and other files of the Department; also includes retail sales records.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence and other files of the Department; also includes retail sales records.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Agriculture.; Cornell University; Cornell University.
Subjects:
Dairying -- Study and teaching.; Dairying -- Study and teaching
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
This collection includes collection #21-20-81.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence and Department Files
  - 1903-10-1905-12 (Box 1)
  - 1906-01-1906-12 (Box 2)
  - 1907-01-1907-12 (Box 3)
  - 1908-01-1908-12 (Box 4)
  - 1909-01-1910-05 (Box 5)
  - 1910-06-1911-06 (Box 6)
  - 1911-07-1912-12 (Box 7)
  - 1913-01-1914-07 (Box 8)
  - 1914-08-1915-04 (Box 9)
  - 1915-05-1915-12 (Box 10)
  - 1916-01-1916-09 (Box 11)
  - 1916-10-1917-06 (Box 12)
  - 1917-07-1918-01 (Box 13)
  - 1918-02-1919-02 (Box 14)
  - 1919-03-1920-03 (Box 15)
  - 1920-04-1920-12 (Box 16)
  - 1921-01-1921-12 (Box 17)
  - 1922-01-1923-06 (Box 18)
  - 1923-07-1924-12 (Box 19)
  - 1925-01-1927-12 (Box 20)
  - 1928-01-1928-12 (Box 21)
  - 1929-01-1930-12 (Box 22)
  - 1931-01-1931-08 (Box 23)
  - 1931-09 (Box 24)
  - 1931-10-1931-11 (Box 25)
  - 1931-12-1932-12 (Box 26)
  - 1933-01-1934-12 (Box 27)
  - Laboratory Manual - Introduction to Dairy Science (Box 27)
  - Masurovsky's Ice Creameter (Box 27)
  - Bacteriology Students - Admission Cards, 1941-1943 (Box 27)
  - Bacteriology Course Packet, 1947 (Box 27)
  - "Controlling Feedy and Barny Odors in Milk" by Brueckner, 1940 (Box 27)
  - "Controlling the Flavor of Pasteurized Milk" by Brueckner, 1941 (Box 27)
  - Department of dairy industry brochure, 1951 (Box 27)
  - "Development of Oxidized Flavors in Unhomogenized and Homogenized Milk" by Guthrie, 1955 (Box 27)
  - "The Manufacture of Modified Skimmed Milk" - by Holland, no date (Box 27)
  - Report for Middle States Association of Colleges - self evaluation prepared by A.W. Gibson, 1956 (Box 27)
  - "What We Have Learned About Bulk Tanks", 1956 (Box 27)
  - Department annual letter to alumni, 1957 (Box 27)
  - "Significant Developments in the Evolution of Public Control of Milk Prices in the New York Milkshed" by Lelan Spencer, 1957 (Box 27)
  - Letter and memos concerning MYVACET distilled acetylated monoglyceride products, 1961 (Box 27)
  - "Bottle-Washing Studies Under Plant Conditions" by Stark, Holland and White, no date (Box 27)
  - "The Construction of a Reliable Bacteriological Incubator" by Stark, no date (Box 27)
  - Milk dating in New York City by Dahlberg, no date (Box 27)
  - 1935-01-1935-12 (Box 28)
  - 1936-01-1938-12 (Box 29)
  - 1939-01-1939-03 (Box 30)
  - 1939-04-1939-12 (Box 31)
  - 1940-01-1940-07 (Box 32)
  - 1940-08-1940-09 (Box 33)
  - 1940-10-1940-11 (Box 34)
  - 1940-12-1942-01 (Box 35)
  - 1942-02-1942-03 (Box 36)
  - 1942-04-1942-12 (Box 37)
  - 1943-01-1943-03 (Box 38)
  - 1943-04-1943-12 (Box 39)
  - 1944-01-1944-09 (Box 40)
  - 1944-10-1944-12 (Box 41)
  - 1945-01-1945-09 (Box 42)
  - 1945-10-1946-03 (Box 43)